<resources>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">http://m.gronor.com</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_slideshow">My Cart</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">My Orders</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Rate us</string>
    <string name="menu_send">About us</string>
    <string name="aboutus">
        Gronor is India’s largest low price online super-market in the grocery space. The company uses its in-house technology platform to manage a
        network of over 5,000 partner stores  that enable the company to run a fast and lean supply chain – from manufacturers straight to customers
        in 27+ cities namely Agra, Ahmedabad, Aligarh, Allahabad, Asansol,  Bengaluru, Bhiwadi, Chandigarh, Chennai, Delhi, Durgapur, Faridabad, Guwahati,
        Hapur, HR-NCR, Hyderabad, Indore, Jaipur, Kanpur, Kolkata, Lucknow, Meerut, Modinagar, Moradabad, Mumbai, Panipat, Pune, Rohtak, Sonipat, UP-NCR,
        Vadodara, and Zirakpur. Gronor utilizes its efficient supply chain to deliver over 25 million products to customers every month.  A majority of
        these products belong to the company’s 8 in house brands namely  Gronor Happy Day, Gronor Happy Home, Gronor Mothers choice, Gronor Happy Baby,
        G Fresh, O’range and budget brands Savemore and Havemore.

        It is hereby clarified that Gronor India Private Limited does not have any relation with the mark ‘Gronor’,  which (we are given to understand) is used
        by Redstone Consultancy Services Pvt Ltd for its real estate services business, which is not related to Gronor India Private Limited in any manner.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="action_tools">Login</string>
    <string name="search">SEARCH</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps2">Map</string>
</resources>
